We’re finally here.
After being stuck inside the bus for two hours.
There it is!
The beach!
Two nights and three days of summer until school again.
What should I do about turning into a doll at night?
But...
Anyways, it’s the beach!
Okay!
Let's split up into groups and make some curry.
Since the homeroom teacher is ill, I'll sample the food instead.
So please make them tasty.
Yes!
My heart is at ease since Flora-chan is in the same group.
Leave the cooking to me,
I always make it with my papa.
Let’s try our best, Sumomo.
We’re all set.
Alright, I’ll start the fire.
Should Yayoi and Nao-chan cut the vegetables?
Okay.
Alright then Tsuwabuki, you help cook the rice with Yuuki.
With Yuuki?
Can you lift it there a bit, Yayoi?
Okay!
Then let's build the rice.
Build?
Yuuki, what’s wrong?
The word "build" is used when constructing buildings or poems. But this is something you eat.
Then, what do you mean... when you say let's build the rice?
Well, what it means...
Oh yeah, Yuuki is a Stellar Spinear from Figurare.
She probably has never "built" rice before.
I don't understand.
To build rice means to cook rice.
Cook? Then it should be spoken as "to cook," shouldn’t it?
Why say build?
That’s true, but...
Anyway, just leave it as "build".
I still don't understand.
Then observe, I’ll do it.
It's my job too, so I'll try it.
Please teach me how.
Tsuwabuki-ku-
Stir the rice under water, then pour it out.
Akihime.
Akihime-
Y-Yuuki, don’t pour out the rice!
But you said to pour it out!
Just pour out the water!
What will you do if you pour out the rice too?
You should have told me something important like that beforehand.
Wasn’t the meal delicious?
I ate too much.
And?
You see, he remarkably...
What? Stop teasing and just tell me.
Using the road would draw attention...
Yuki-chan?
Owww...
Someone will see us!
Wow, Yuki-chan!
How did you know I was here?
That’s...!
Was there any response from the ring?
I see... Hoshigaoka is pretty far away...
Yuki-chan, you're all dirty.
I fell earlier.
Want to take a bath?
It’s okay, somethi-
But it will stain if you don't bathe soon.
It’s okay! And think...
it'll look strange bringing a doll into the bathroom.
Sumomo?
Sumomo-tan! Let's all take a bath.
What’s that?
Wow! It’s so cute!
Is it Sumomo-tan’s?
It got dirty so I was going to wash it.
Good view, good view!
Toua! You’re in plain sight!
It’s okay! Akino should come here too.
I’ll stay here.
I said come here! It’s fine!
Sumomo, you brought the doll with you?
No, Yuki-chan came here on his own.
The doll came... on its own?
Mysterious isn’t it?
It really is a mysterious sheep doll.
S-Surely I won’t suddenly turn back into human, will I?
This feels great!
Yuki-chan.
Are you okay?
I-It surprised me.
But because of Non-tan’s breast catch I was saved!
Breast catch...
Noboku, did they grow again?
It’s still the same, F-cup.
Lucky, I’m jealous.
There, there.
Sumomo-chan will get bigger too.
I hope so...
Yuki-chan!
Preparations okay!
Canned juice okay!
Cookies check.
Alright! And now let the pajama party begin!
So, what should we do?
Spine-chilling horror experience stories?
Nobuko, these situations are for telling love stories.
Obviously, we should tell love stories.
Right? Yuuki-san?
I-Is that so?
Well then, love stories?
Anyone with a boyfriend?
No one has one...
Let's talk about what types we like, then.
Nobuko-san, what kind of person do you like?
Let's see...
I guess I like someone who treasures me the most.
I agree!
Me too!
I guess girls like these kind of stories.
Hey, hey, I want to hear Nako-san’s story.
Then Yaeno-san, is there someone you like?
No one yet, but...
I do want to fall in love.
If there is someone you love sincerely...
I think you would be happy.
It seems so...
If I were to think of that person, my heart would start pounding.
It would be fun everyday.
Well...
Sumomo-chan, looks like you’re in love.
There is someone, right? Someone you like.
Who is it, who is it? Tell us!
Someone from our school? Same class?
Now now, come on.
Spill it. We’ll help you out.
Excuse me.
Is everyone sleeping?
No...
Somehow it looks like a lot of fun.
But it’s time to sleep, so everyone please return to your rooms.
Okay...
Akihime has someone she likes...
You don’t look too well, Tsuwabuki-kun.
What happened?
I'm just tired.
I was very nervous that my doll form would get found out yesterday.
Is that all?
Yep, that's all.
Really?
Well, tonight's the first day of the month, so you won't transform.
There is going to be a courage test, so rest well.
Well then...
It doesn’t matter who Akihime likes.
Okay!
Male students who are taking the courage test, draw from the raffle to pick their partners.
Excuse me...
Tsuwabuki-kun...
Are you okay?
Sakuraba said that you slept because you were sick.
I'm fine.
That’s a relief.
Akihime.
Well...
Akihime-san! You’re partnered with me, pleased to work with you.
Yes! Pleased to work with you.
Yuuki again...
You know...
Yuuki is...
Well...
Yuuki?
I wonder what's wrong. She hadn't said anything earlier.
Did I... make her mad?
Yuuki, by any chance, are you scared?
No, of course not...
Alright! Big success!
Yuuki-san, nice reaction!
But, Tsuwabuki-kun didn’t look scared at all.
I knew it wasn't real.
He’s no fun.
Flora, Yaeno-san, let's go on.
Okay.
Let's go!
Yuuki, are you okay?
I’m fine, something like this...
What...
Yuuki?
W-Why?
If you can’t stand up, I’ll give you a ride.
I'm fine!
It would be better than just staying here.
I-I understand...
Is it here? Or maybe there?
How about here?
I’m fine now, please let me down.
U-Umm...
I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
Please keep this a secret.
I got it.
Haru!
Thank God...
That was really dangerous.
It’s a single road. So how exactly did you get lost?
Well, I have no excuse.
Of course, Yuuki-san...
It's about Tsuwabuki-kun...
And Tsuwabuki-kun about Yuuki-san...
Sumomo!
She was...
...avoiding me.
Akihime...
Why does it have to be the first day of the month tonight?
Akihime?
I’m sorry!
Tsuwabuki-kun? I didn’t know you were here...
W-Why are you here?
I-I couldn’t fall asleep, so...
Me neither.
The stars...
Hey...
B-Because it’s the first day of the month...
The stars are easy to see.
The stars?
They really are!
The twinkling looks as if they're talking to each other.
I'm sorry. I said something weird.
It's funny, isn’t it?
N-No, not at all.
Actually, I know why the stars twinkle.
Although it may not look like that to me, like how the stars are talking...
To be able to see it like that, I think is incredible.
S-Something like that isn’t incredible at all.
It is incredible.
That star’s light...
The light you see right now, is very old.
For a light from a star to take thousands of years to reach Earth...
That's what I've learned before.
But, the light you see now may be the star's last light.
That star might already be gone, and cease to exist.
Although to tell you the truth, I really don't know...
A-Akihime?
Oh um, I'm sorry...
What’s wrong?
It’s nothing.
It’s just that... Thinking that star might already be gone,
I became sad.
There is someone, right? Someone you like.
Tsuwabuki-kun?
I-I’m sorry. I suddenly started crying...
I'm sorry...
From that point on, nothing more was said.
There was no need for Akihime to apologize.
Akihime did nothing wrong.
Then, why did I...
By the way, Sumomo-chan and Tsuwabuki-kun...
Don’t you guys feel frustrated?
Like or dislike?
Which is it? Which?!
But finally...
It’s here!
The time of confession!
Eh!? It’s here?
And so, which is it?